kathykuohome.com 2019-03-26

# Privacy Notice | Kathy Kuo Home

CUSTOMER SERVICE

Contact Us

Shipping

Returns

Damages

Product Review Policy

Privacy Notice

Terms & Conditions

Gift Cards

ORDERING

Price Match Guarantee

Canceling an Order

Payment & Stock Status

MY ACCOUNT

My Account Information

My Order History

My Addresses

My Pay Methods

My Wishlist

My Reviews

ABOUT KATHY KUO HOME

About Us

Our Trade Program

Our Services

Our Products

Press & Media

| 

**We commit ourselves to your security and privacy.**

Kathy Kuo Home values our customers and respects your privacy. This privacy policy (“Policy”) describes the personal information we collect, why we collect it, how we use and protect it, and when we share it with third parties. Our Policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. By providing your personal information to Kathy Kuo Home, you consent to the manner in which we collect, use, disclose, protect and otherwise manage that information.

If our information practices change, we will post an updated version of the Policy on the Kathy Kuo Home Website (“Website”). You can tell if the Policy has changed by checking the “Last Updated” date that appears below and that will be the date on which the new Policy becomes effective. You may exercise your choices about how we collect and use your information consistent with this Policy at any time. If you have any questions about our Policy, please contact us as described in the section below entitled, "How do I contact you?"

This Policy Was Last Updated May 1, 2017.

**What personal information does Kathy Kuo home collect?**

We may collect personal information from you (such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, or credit card number) when you visit our Website, place an order online or by phone, save your information with us online, contact us with a question or concern, participate in a contest, promotion, or survey, etc. 

When you access or use www.kathykuohome.com, we automatically collect information about you, including:

**Log Information:**  We log information about your use of the Services, including your access times, pages viewed, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type and language and the website you visited before navigating to our Services. We may also infer your geographic location based on your IP address.

**Device Information:**  We collect information about the computer or mobile device you use to access our Services, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers and mobile network information.

**Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:**  We use various technologies to collect information, and this may include sending cookies to your computer or mobile device. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us to, among other things, improve our services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular and count visits. You may choose to disable your cookies at any time. 

We also maintain a record of your product interests and the purchases you make online or by phone. We may combine all of this information with information about you that we acquire from our joint marketing partners and from unrelated third parties.

**How does Kathy Kuo Home use my information?**

We may use your personal information for one or more of the following reasons:

  * To process and fulfill your order, including sending you emails to confirm your order status and shipment;
  * To communicate with you and to send you information by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means about our products, services, contests, and promotions, unless you have directed us not to contact you with promotional communications;
  * To administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions;
  * To help us learn more about your shopping preferences;
  * To help us address problems with and improve our site design, products and services;
  * To enhance your shopping experience through our Website;
  * To analyze trends and statistics;
  * To protect the security or integrity of our Website and our business; and/or
  * To contact you if necessary.;
  * To send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;
  * To respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;
  * To personalize and improve the Services and provide advertisements, content or features that match your profile and interests;
  * To carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.

**Does Kathy Kuo Home share my personal information?**

We may share your personal information for one or more of the following reasons:

  * We may share your information with our service providers who manage our customer information and perform services on our behalf, such as fulfilling promotions, sending communications to our customers, conducting surveys, etc. We do not authorize any of these service providers to make any other use or disclosure of your information.
  * We may share your information when we team up with another company to jointly offer or provide products, services, contests, or promotions to our customers.
  * We may share your information to comply with laws or regulations or in response to a valid subpoena, order, or government request, or to protect the rights of Kathy Kuo Home and others.

**Do you use my information to send me promotional materials?**

Kathy Kuo Home wants to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive promotional information, such as information about special offers and sales events, you can let us know by contacting us as described in the section below entitled, "How do I contact you?"

If you ask us to remove your name and address from all or certain promotional lists, we will maintain your name on a “do not contact” list so that we can honor your request. It may take up to 10 days to process your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from Kathy Kuo Home. If you change your mind, you can start receiving promotional communications from us again by contacting us.

Please note that we use Google Analytics cross device services and other third party analytics tools to serve you targeted and remarketing advertising.  

Please note that when you make an online purchase from us, we will continue to confirm your order status and shipment by email. We may also need to contact you via telephone, email or postal mail with questions or information regarding your order.

**How does Kathy Kuo Home protect kids’ privacy?**

Kathy Kuo Home is concerned about the privacy and safety of children when they use the Internet. We will never knowingly request or collect personal information online from anyone under the age of 13. Our Website is a general audience site and is not targeted to or intended for use by children. If you are a parent and believe we may have inadvertently collected such information from your child, please notify us immediately by sending an email or phoning us toll free at 1.888.908.2925.

**Does my privacy change if I click a link to another website?**

For your convenience and information, our Website and emails may contain links to other sites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked site. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any site that you access through our Website.

**How does Kathy Kuo Home use advertising?**

We may use third-party advertising companies to place Kathy Kuo Home ads on third party sites that link back to our Website. Please note that these companies may use information about your visit to our Website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements on third party sites that link to our Website or App, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**How does Kathy Kuo Home use cookies?**

We use "cookies," which are small data files that are stored on your computer’s hard drive when you visit a website. Cookies enable you to shop on our Website and may be used in a variety of ways to enhance or personalize your online browsing and shopping experience. Cookies may also be used to collect transaction information needed by a scrip or loyalty program to which you have authorized us to provide your personal information.

You can set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept it. If you set your browser not to accept cookies, you will need to call Customer Service toll free at 1.888.908.2925 in order to place your order.

**How does Kathy Kuo Home collect, share, and use information and photos from my social media accounts?**

We encourage our customers to share and connect with us on social media (including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest, Polyvore, Google+, Tumblr, and YouTube). If you upload user-generated content to your social media accounts which you tag with our branded handle or hashtags, Kathy Kuo Home may collect that content, including your photo, social media username, caption information (if any) and location information (if any). By using our branded handle or hashtag, you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure, and other uses of your post information. We may use this collected information to customize the content we show you and our customers, including advertisements, promotions, and marketing campaigns. 

**How does Kathy Kuo Home keep my information secure?**

We take precautions, including the use of encryption technologies and authentication tools, to protect the security of your personal information and to provide you with a safe and convenient shopping experience. We have in place certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial safeguards to protect the security and privacy of your personal information.

If for any reason you cannot access a secure server, or if you're not comfortable shopping online, please feel free to place your order by calling our Customer Service representatives at 1.888.908.2925 (toll free). Some browsers and firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers. In that case, you will be unable to connect to our server so you will not have to worry about mistakenly placing an order through an unsecured connection.

**How do I contact you?**

For questions about our Privacy Policy, to make choices about receiving promotional communications, to update your personal information, or to place an order, you can contact Kathy Kuo Home by email or telephone.

Email: cs@kathykuohome.com   Call: 1.888.908.2925 (toll free).

| 

MORE WAYS TO REACH US

Call Us

Hours

9am to 6pm EST Mon. to Fri.

Email

cs@kathykuohome.com

Online Message  
  
---|---|---
